(Leonard:)Not mad at the elves at all.
(Leonard:)Open it.
Okay. Ahem.
"An examination of the economic,
cultural and political roots of slavery...
...in the Old South, 1619 to 1865."
(Penny:)What the hell is this?
Don't ask me, a little elf did it. Ha, ha.
(Penny:)So let me get this straight.
(Penny:)You just assumed my paper would be bad,
so you wrote one for me?
(Leonard:)- I assumed it would be good. Then I read it.
- What?
Well, I mean, it was good. There were just
a few things that needed a little polishing.
- Well, you changed every word.
- That's not true. Uh...
"Slavery."
Uh, "1619." Your name at the top.
That's all you.
(Penny:)You are such an ass.
This is why I didn't wanna tell you
I was taking a class.
(Leonard:)Please, don't be upset. I just...